Pelosi calls on the FBI to investigate pro-Palestinian protesters for Russian ties.
You know, I had decided this morning that I need to definitely start my day without looking at my phone first because of crazy shit like this.
Yes, because this crazy bitch done lost some motherfucking mind.
And I don't want to start my day with crazy bitches losing their mind.
I want to start my day walking my dog.
You know what I'm saying?
That's what I want to do.
Cutting my bangs.
You know, that's what I want to do.
I also started my day with my morning musings like I do every morning on my Patreon, you know, just to help us get into a good sense of things, get into a good rhythm.
You know, they call me the common sense specialist.
So I try and start my day with common sense and try and start y'all day with common sense and not with fuckery like this lady.
Let me tell you something about white women.
Baby, when y'all are on a mission, y'all can really make things happen.
It's unfortunate, though, how so many of y'all be on the wrong fucking mission.
Good morning.